<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">

  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>Returnal</title>
      <link href="https://housemarque.com/games/returnal" />
      <description>
        After crash-landing on this shape-shifting world, Selene must search 
        through the barren landscape of an ancient civilization for her escape. 
        Isolated and alone, she finds herself fighting tooth and nail for survival. 
        Again and again, she's defeated forced to restart her journey every time she dies.
      </description>
      <pubdate>Fri, 06 April 2010 14:58:07 +0000</pubdate>
    </item>


    <item>
      <title>Sonys Acquisition Of Bungie</title>
      <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/2/1/22912075/sony-bungie-acquisition-fortnite-playstation-destiny-live-service-games" />
      <description>
        Microsoft has Minecraft, Epic Games has Fortnite, and Sony now has Destiny. 
        In a $3.6 billion deal, Sony is acquiring Bungie, the game studio famous for 
        creating the Halo and Destiny universes. It's a big deal, in a month already full 
        of massive deals. It's also backed by some equally big promises from Bungie 
        about its independence, the future of Destiny, and commitments to multiplatform games.
      </description>
      <pubdate>Sat, 28 January 2004 17:36:24 +0000</pubdate>
    </item>


    <item>
      <title>Martha Is Dead</title>
      <link href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/paultassi/2022/02/12/why-playstation-is-censoring-horror-game-martha-is-dead/?sh=1cd744685457" />
      <description>
        They say that all press is good press, and case in point, I'd never even 
        heard of the game Martha is Dead until it started making headlines for Sony 
        demanding that parts of it be cut in order for release on PlayStation.
      </description>
      <pubdate>Mon, 16 June 2012 13:45:37 +0000</pubdate>
    </item>


    <item>
      <title>Attack on titan</title>
      <link href="https://www.polygon.com/22924079/anime-awards-winners-list-2022-crunchyroll" />
      <description>
        Crunchyroll has announced the winners of its sixth annual Anime Awards, 
        which honor the anime's best shows, voice actors, animators, and creators of 
        the past year. Attack on Titan Final Season Part 1 took home the prize 
        for Anime of the Year this time around and secured four wins in total, including 
        Best Antagonist, for Eren Jaeger, Best Opening Sequence, and Best Japanese Voice 
        Acting Performance.
      </description>
      <pubdate>Wed, 01 May 2011 04:08:57 +0000</pubdate>
    </item>


    <item>
      <title>Black Cover</title>
      <link href="https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/cowboy-bebop-canceled-netflix-1235060256/" />
      <description>
        Insiders pointed out that Netflix's renewal rate for scripted series 
        that have two or more seasons stands at 60 percent, in line with industry 
        averages, and, like all Netflix renewal verdicts, the decision was made by 
        balancing the show's viewership and cost. The streamer also prides itself 
        on taking big swings on projects like Cowboy Bebop and has many other 
        genre shows on the air and in the works.
      </description>
      <pubdate>Fri, 06 April 2008 14:58:07 +0000</pubdate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>